Guide to the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VIII. Member & Subscriber Services, 1995-2003
  - Subseries VIII.2 Membership Files, 1995-2002
    - Catholic Values Investment Trust (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Christian Brothers Investment Services (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Christian Church (Disciples of Christ) (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Christian Church Foundation (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Christus Health (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Church of the Brethen
      - Benefit Fund (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Benefit Trust (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Church Pension Fund, The (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Church Women United (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Citizens Trust (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Clean Yield (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Conference on Corporate Responsibility of IN-MI (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Congregation of the Passion (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Congregation of the Sisters of St. Agnes (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Congregation of the Sisters of Charity of the Incarnate Word, Houston (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Congregation of the Sisters of the Holy Cross (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Daughters of Charity National Health System (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Domini Social Index Fund (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Eastern Mercy Health System (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Education Foundation of America, The (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - ELAS (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - Episcopal Church (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - Episcopal Church Pension Board (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - Episcopal Church Publishing Company (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - Episcopal Diocese of Massachusetts (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - Ethical Funds (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - Evangelical Lutheran Church in America (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - Fidelity Bank (Box 31, Folder 56)
    - First Union Bank (Box 31, Folder 57)
    - F.L. Putnam Management Company (Box 31, Folder 58)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 31, Folder 59)
    - Fox Asset Management (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - Franciscan Health System (Box 31, Folder 61)
    - Franciscan, Holy Name Province (Box 31, Folder 62)
    - Franciscan Missionaries of Mary Provincialate, Rome, Italy (Box 31, Folder 63)
    - Franklin Research and Development (Box 31, Folder 64)
    - Friars of the Atonement (Box 31, Folder 65)
    - Friends, Ivory & Sime (Box 31, Folder 66)
    - Foundation for Deep Ecology (Box 31, Folder 67)
    - G. Pier Luigi (Box 31, Folder 68)
    - Harrington Investment Associates, Inc. (Box 31, Folder 69)
    - HKM Foundation (Box 31, Folder 70)
    - Holy Cross Health Care System (Box 31, Folder 71)
    - Holy Name Province (Box 31, Folder 72)
    - Hospital of San Rafael (Box 31, Folder 73)
    - Illinois Committee for Responsible Investment (Box 31, Folder 74)
    - Immaculate Heart Mission Inc. (Box 31, Folder 75)
    - Independence Investment (Box 31, Folder 76)
    - Integral Management, Inc. (Box 31, Folder 77)
    - Invesco Global Asset Management (Box 31, Folder 78)
    - Jessie Smith Noyes Foundation (Box 31, Folder 79)
    - Jesuit Conference USA, Office of Social Ministries (Box 31, Folder 80)
    - Johnson & Johnson (Box 31, Folder 81)
    - Justice Organizers, Leadership & Treasurers Coalition (JOLT) (Box 31, Folder 82)
    - Laird Norton Trust Company (Box 31, Folder 83)
    - Levis Strauss (Box 31, Folder 84)
    - Marianist Society (Box 31, Folder 85)
    - Marin Institute (Box 31, Folder 86)
    - Maryknoll Fathers and Brothers (Box 31, Folder 87)
    - MBE Development and Investment Forum (Box 31, Folder 88)
    - McHugh Associates, Inc. (Box 31, Folder 89)
    - Medical Mission Sisters (Box 31, Folder 90)
    - Mellon Equity (Box 31, Folder 91)
    - Mennonite Mutual Aid (Box 31, Folder 92)
    - Mercy Consolidated Asset Management (Box 31, Folder 93)
    - Mid-Atlantic Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (Box 31, Folder 94)
    - Mid-West Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (Box 31, Folder 95)
    - Miller, Howard (Box 31, Folder 96)
    - Minnesota Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (Box 31, Folder 97)
    - Missionaries of Africa (Box 31, Folder 98)
    - Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate (Box 31, Folder 99)
    - Mongoven (Box 31, Folder 100)
    - National Association for Treasurers of Religious Institutes (Box 31, Folder 101)
    - National Council of Churches (Box 31, Folder 102)
    - National Wildlife Foundation (Box 31, Folder 103)
    - Neuberger & Berman (Box 31, Folder 104)
    - New England Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (Box 31, Folder 105)
    - New World Foundation, The (Box 31, Folder 106)
    - New York City Office of the Comptroller (Box 31, Folder 107)
    - New York / Connecticut Foundation of the United Methodist Church (Box 31, Folder 108)
    - NFJ Investment Group (Box 31, Folder 109)
    - Northwest Coalition for Responsible Investment (NCRI) (Box 31, Folder 110)
    - Ohio Valley Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (Box 31, Folder 111)
    - Oneida Trust (Box 31, Folder 112)
    - Oppenheimer Capital (Box 31, Folder 113)
    - Overseas Missionary Center (Box 31, Folder 114)
    - Paxworld (Box 31, Folder 115)
    - Philadelphia Area Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (Box 31, Folder 116)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen Corporation (Box 31, Folder 117)
    - Presbyterian Church USA (Box 31, Folder 118)
    - Progressive Securities (Box 31, Folder 119)
    - Providencia Prima (Box 31, Folder 120)
    - Proxy Monitor (Box 31, Folder 121)
    - Rabbinical Pension Board (Box 31, Folder 122)
    - Raynham (Box 31, Folder 123)
    - Reebok (Box 31, Folder 124)
    - Reformed Church in America (Box 31, Folder 125)
    - Region VI Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (Box 31, Folder 126)
    - Rio Trueba Gestion (Box 31, Folder 127)
    - Roxbury Capital Management (in same file as above) (Box 31, Folder 128)
    - Riverside Church, The (Box 31, Folder 129)
    - Rockefeller & Co., Inc. (Box 31, Folder 130)
    - St. Joseph Health System (Box 31, Folder 131)
    - St. Mary of the Springs (Box 31, Folder 132)
    - St. Walburg Monastery (Box 31, Folder 133)
    - Scudder, Stevens & Clark (Box 31, Folder 134)
    - Shefa Fund, The (Box 31, Folder 135)
    - Sinsinawa Dominicans (Box 31, Folder 136)
    - School Sisters of Notre Dame Cooperative Investment Fund (Box 31, Folder 137)
    - Sisters of Charity of St. Elizabeth (Box 31)
    - Sisters of Charity of St. Vincent de Paul of New York (Box 31, Folder 140)
    - Sisters of Charity of St. Vincent de Paul, Halifax, Nova Scotia (Box 31, Folder 141)
    - Sisters of Charity of the Blessed Virgin Mary (Box 31, Folder 142)
    - Sisters of Charity of the Incarnate Word Health Care System, Houston (Box 31, Folder 143)
    - Sisters of Loretto (Box 31, Folder 144)
    - Sisters of Mercy, North Carolina Foundation (2 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Sisters of Mercy, Regional Community of Detroit (2 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Sisters of St. Benedict (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Sisters of St. Francis (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Sisters of St. Joseph of Wheeling (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Sisters of the Holy Cross, Indiana (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Sisters of the Holy Names (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Sisters of the Humility of Mary (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Sisters of the Sorrowful Mother (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Smith Barney Asset Management (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Socially Responsible Investment Coalition (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - South Shore Bank (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Springfield Dominican Sisters (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - State of Connecticut (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - State of Wisconsin (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Stein Roe & Farnham (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Texas Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - TIAA-Cref (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Tri-State Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (New York, Connecticut, and New Jersey) (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Trillium Asset Management (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Trinity Church (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Unitarian Universalist Association (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Unitarian Universalist Service Committee (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - United Church of Christ
      - Board for World Ministries (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - Board of Home Ministries (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - United Methodist Church
      - Board of Church and Society (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Foundation (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - General Board of Global Ministries (GBGM)
        - National Division (Box 32, Folder 30)
        - Women’s Division (Box 32, Folder 31)
        - World Division (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - General Board of Pension and Health Benefits (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - United Methodist City Society (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - U.S. Trust Company, Boston (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - U.S. Trust Company of New York (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Walden Capital Management (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Western New York Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - William Caspar Graustein Memorial Fund (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Wisconsin Coalition for Responsible Investment (CRI) (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - World Asset Management (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - YMCA (Box 32, Folder 42)
- Series IX. Communications and Publicity, 1971-1999 [Bulk Dates: 1971-1979 1996]
  This series includes general communications files, as well as brochures, clippings, press releases, and promotional materials.
  - General
    - CBS--60 Minutes Profile on ICCR, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Conscientious Investors Guide, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Corporate Examiner--Renewal Cards, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - ICCR Brochures, 1980s (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - ICCR Memos/Outreach Materials on South Africa, 1980s (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Promotional Mailings for Corporate Examiner, Proxy Book, Alternative Investments Packet, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Publications--Informational Letters on ICCR Publications, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Press, 1981-1984 (5 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Press Clippings
    - General
      - 1971-1972 (2 Folders) (Box 49, Folder 1 to 2)
      - 1974-1979 (19 Folders) (Box 49, Folder 3 to 21)
      - 1996 (Box 81, Folder 24)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous, 1974-1979 (9 Folders) (Box 50, Folder 1 to 9)
    - CIC Military and Church Investments Report, Press on, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Fifteenth Anniversary, 1971-1985 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Greyhound, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - History, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Human Resources Network, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Namibia and Oil, 1973-1975 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Proxy Resolutions--Press, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Samples Gen. Article, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Tobacco
      - General, 1987-1994 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Advertising, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases
    - 1972 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - 1976-1978 (3 Folders) (Box 50, Folder 19 to 21)
    - 1984 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Series X. Audiovisual Materials, 2000-2002, Undated
  This series consists of a few audiovisual materials related to ICCR, including audio and video recordings of talks and seminars.
  - ICCR Package, Undated, (VHS Videotape TRT 2:45) (Box 35)
  - ICCR Seminar on Blueprint for Change: Corporate Governance for the Future, 2002 September 19, (Compact Disc (Audio) ) (Box 35)
  - Religion in the News-Tim Smith, Undated, (Audiocassette) (Box 35)
    (Paulist Communications #791-792)
  - “Weaponization of the Heavens,” Talk Given by Karl Grossman at ICCR Militarism & Violence Resolution Issue Group, 2000 February 2, (VHS Videotape) (Box 35)
- Series XI. General Organizational Records, 1986-2011
  This series contains a small amount of executive director records and organizational files related to financial matters, strategic planning, and general files on socially responsible investing.
  - Bond, Patrick. Papers, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Executive Director Wolf’s Files
    - General Subjects
      - Central Finance Board of Methodist Church, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Corporate Governance
        - Conference on, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 2)
        - Votes for Board of Directors, Undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Free Prior Informed Consent (FPIC), 2005 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Global Warming, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HIV Reporting, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Living Wage, 2000-2001 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Native American Images, 2001-2002 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Pay Equity/Pay Disparity, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Pharmaceutical Meeting, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Pharmaceutical Pricing, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Project K, Undated (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Public Relations/HIV/AIDS, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Stock Options - Corporate Examiner (CE), 2001-2005 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Violent Video Games, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Companies
      - Abbot
        - Drug Pricing, 2001-2005 (Box 73, Folder 16)
        - PCV’s, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - AT&T, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - BP Amoco, 2000-2001 (Box 73, Folder 19)
      - Bristol Myers/Squibb, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - Cisco, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Citigroup, 2001-2003 (Box 73, Folder 22)
      - Coca-Cola, 2001-2003 (Box 73, Folder 23)
      - Exxon Mobil, 2003, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - Ford, circa 2005 (Box 73, Folder 25)
      - GAP (Social Responsibility Report), 2004 (Box 73, Folder 26)
      - Halliburton, 2005-2006 (Box 73, Folder 27)
      - Merck
        - Domestic Equality, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 28)
        - Drug Pricing, 2001-2002 (Box 73, Folder 29)
      - Pepsico, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 30)
      - Pfizer
        - General, 2003-2005 (Box 73, Folder 31)
        - Drug Pricing, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 32)
      - Proctor & Gamble, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 33)
      - Shell--Dialogue on Sustainable Development, 1999-2002 (Box 73, Folder 34)
      - Time Warner--Smoke Free Movies, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 35)
      - Tootsie Roll, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 36)
      - Walmart--Resolution and Correspondence, 1992-1993, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 37)
      - Wendy’s--Court Case, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Folder 38)
  - Financial Files
    - Finance Committee
      - 1993-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Memos, 1995-1998 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Report, 1995 February (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Financial Reports, 1995 June-1997 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Watson Rice, 1996-1997 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Grants--The Energy Foundation, 2002-2004 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - ICCR Fundraising, 2002-2009 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - ICCR Internship Program, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - ICCR Strategic Plan, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Meetings, 2008 February (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Pharmaceuticals--Minutes, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Planning Committee & Survey Reports, 1997 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Prayer Services, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Schilling, David--Speeches/Articles, 1998-2011 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Socially Responsible Investing (SRI)
    - Anti-Socially Responsible Investing / Corporate Social Responsibility (SRI/CSR) Articles, 2003-2005 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Colleges and Universities, 2003-2004 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Foundations, 2003-2008 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - France, 2000-2004 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Media--General, 2003-2007 (2 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Non-Governmental Organizations (NGOs)--Program on Corporations, Law & Democracy (POCLAD) Corporate Reform, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Philanthropy’s Vision: A Leadership Summit, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Political Accountability, Center for (CPA)
      - Campaign Contributions & Lobbying, 2006-2007 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Publications, circa 2006 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Political Accountability Working Group, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Proxy Advisory Services, 2004-2007 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Shareholder Filing Guidelines
      - ICCR Shareholding Filing Guidelines, 1998-2002 (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - Guidelines for Shareholder Engagement, Undated (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Socially Responsible Investing (SRI)Industry, 2003-2004 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Trends Report (Forum for Socially Responsible Investing (SIF), 2001-2007 (Box 76, Folder 16)